A Guide to the Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution Agency Head Correspondence and Subject Files, 1980-2012
Library of Virginia
- Agency head correspondence and subject files, 1980-2006.
  - Accession 43552, 1980-2006.
    - Virginia Public Service Reward and Recognition Steering Committee (McPhie), 2000. (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Virginia Quick Reference Directory, January 10, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Virginia School at Hampton (Grievance Procedure), n.d.. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives #1, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Supreme Court, HO Meeting, December 5, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Trial Lawyers Association, 1998. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Virginia's Executive Management Letter, March 1987. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Virginia's Handbook on Planning and Performance, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Virginia's Legislative Process, 1994. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Visually Handicapped, 1992. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - VITA--Information, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - VITA Meeting--9-11 a.m., March 5, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - VITA Meeting, March 22, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Voice Mail Information, 1998. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Voluntary Payroll Deduction Options, n.d.. (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - VPBB Facilitation, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - VPI and SU, 1997. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - VRS, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - VRS-VIPS-VRS Benefits, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "W", 1995. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - W-9 Forms, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Wage Employment, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Waltz, Rita R., July 8, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Wellford, Yvonne S., July 9, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Whistleblower Protection, 1995. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Worker's Compensation, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Workers' Compensation and ADA, 1999. (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Workers' Compensation Plan, 2000. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Workforce Commission, May 26, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Workforce Commission, July 7, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Workforce Commission Report, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Workmen's Compensation Act, 1997-1998. (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Workmen's Compensation Information, 1999. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Workplace Hypotheticals, April 9, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Workplace Investigations, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Workplace Investigations, May 14, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Workplace Reduction (Executive Order, etc.), 1994. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Workshop, May 24, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - WTA, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - WTA Appeal Process, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - WTA--DERC, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - WTA--PMIS, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - "X-Y-Z", 1995. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Accession 44014, ADD DATE.
    This accession is arranged in its original order, possessing no discernible arrangement.
    - January-October 1994. (Box 5)
    - November-December 1994. (Box 4)
    - January-July 1995. (Box 3)
    - August-December 1995. (Box 2)
    - January-December 1996. (Box 1)
    - January-December 1997. (Box 8)
    - January-December 1998. (Box 7)
    - ABC, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Abingdon, May 23, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Agency Replies, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Aging/Children/Health Planning/Health Services Cost Review Council, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services, n.d.. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Air Pollution, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Annandale, May 3, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Arts/Library--Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Budget Proposals, 2000 Legislation, November 22, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - A Businessman's Guide to the Problems of Drugs and Alcohol in the Workplace, n.d.. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Central Support Systems: A Direction for the 1990's, September 1989. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Certification Correspondence, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign, 1998. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Committee Receipts, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Commonwealth Attorney's Services and Training Council, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Compliance--Gordon, Gail W. (Lancaster County Social Services), June 10, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Comptroller, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Constitutional Officers, 1986-1988. (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Contacts and Action Records, 1986. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Contacts and Grievances, 1982-1987. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Contacts, Standards of Conduct, and Virginia Dept. of Corrections' Correspondence, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Corrections/Correctional Education--Capitol Police, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Counselors' Discussions, 2000. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Court Documents on Public School Cases Using AHO's, 1987. (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Daily Activity Reports, Data Sheets, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - DED/DHCD, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Dept. of Health Regulatory Boards, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services--Correspondance and Notes, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1994. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1995. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1996. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1997. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1991 prior. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1994. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1995. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1996. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training Interpretations, 1997. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Dept. for Rights of the Disabled, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - DERC--Activity Report, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - DERC--Annual Reports and Data Sheets, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - DERC--Correspondence, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - DERC--Correspondence, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - DERC--Correspondence, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - DERC--Correspondence, Memos and News Clippings, 1998-1999. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - DERC--Grievance Procedure--"Major Problem with Whole System", July 1994. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - DERC--Legislative Proposal Draft, 2000 Legislation, August 23, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - DERC--Legislative Proposals on Appeals, 2000 Legislation, December 22 and 29, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - DERC--Memos, Correspondence, Legislation and Finances, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - DERC--Operations, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - DERC--Patrons for Legislative Proposals, 2000 Legislation, December 29, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - DERC--Proposed Decision Packages Draft, 2000 Legislation, September 7, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - DERC--Supreme Court Correspondence, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - DERC Task Force Meeting--Effectiveness of the Grievance Procedure, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - DMV, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - DMV, 1997. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - DOT, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - DPT, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Drug Abuse Correspondence and Drug Policy, 1990-1991. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Drug Abuse Resources, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Drug-Free Awareness, 1989-1990. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Drug-Free Workplace, 1987. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Drug-Free Workplace, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Drug-Free Workplace, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Drug-Free Workplace, 1991-1992. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Drug-Free Workplace--Articles, etc., 1989. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Drug-Free Workplace--Correspondence, 1989-1996. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Drug-Free Workplace--Federal Register, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Drug-Free Workplace--Substance Abuse Policy, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Drug Policy, September 4, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Drug Testing, 1988-1989. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Education--Various State Colleges, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Employee Grievance Procedure Task Force Meeting Agenda, May 17, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Employee Notification, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Facilitation's Packet, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Final Proposed Legislation Packages, 2000 Legislation, September 10, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Financial, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - FOIA Request--Goins, Edith (MH/MR), 1986. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Forestry/Water Control Board, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Fredericksburg, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Fredericksburg, May 25, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - General Services, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Geographic and Biological Land-Use Information and Mapping Systems Study, 1989, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Commission on Government: Blue Ribbon Task Force, October 6, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Commission on Government: Blue Ribbon Task Force--Final Report to the Governor, November 15, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Symposium on Virginia's Economic and Budget Outlook, November 13, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Working Papers, Training and Legislative Sessions, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Grant Request, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Appeals, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Grievance Procedure, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedure--Bills and Correspondence, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Grievance Procedure Brochure Draft, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Grievance Procedure--Comments, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Grievance Procedure Draft, May 1989. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Grievance Procedure Draft, May 18, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedure Forms and Correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Grievance Procedure Handbooks, Memos and Correspondence, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Grievance Procedure Notes, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Grievance Procedure Notes, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Grievance Procedure Surveys, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedure Task Force, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Grievance Procedure Task Force, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Grievance Procedure Task Force, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Grievance Procedure Task Force--Miscellaneous, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Harrisonburg, May 18, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Hearing Officer Elections, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Hearing Officers--Comments, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Hearings on Grievance Procedure Policies, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Hearings--Space, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - HRO--Richmond, March 31, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - IHRIS Focus Group, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Information Requested Regarding DERC Legislative Proposals, 2000 Legislation, December 13, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Initial Study for State Grievance Procedure, June 13, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Interpretation--Aliceburg, Jacqueline, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Interpretation--Basden, Barbara C., 1988. (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Interpretation--Bockes, Nancy (Social Services), February 1, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Interpretation--Bowser, Charles E. (NSU), September 1, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Interpretation--Browning, L. E. (Transportation), 1987. (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Interpretation--Bulls, Michael, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Interpretation--Carter, Glenda R. (Health), July 18, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Interpretation--Crotts, Jamie, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Interpretation--Drummond, George W., Jr. (Corrections), October 19, 1997. (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Interpretation--General, no name, October 17, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Interpretation--George, Robert W., September 25, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Interpretation--Glass, Carol (Health), July 20, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Interpretation--Gohanna, Lucy J. (UVA), April 8, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Interpretation--Gordan, William, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Interpretation--Guthrie, Elizabeth L., June 4, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Interpretation--Hogan, Brian (Taxation), October 3, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Interpretation--Johnson, Buretta, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Interpretation--Jones, Bessie S., 1988. (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Interpretation--Jones, John H., April 21, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Interpretation--Jones, Nancy C. (MH/MR/SAS), November 5, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Interpretation--Kaye, William E. (MH/MR/SAS), July 25, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Interpretation--Koehl, Theodore (William and Mary), August 24, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Interpretation--Lukezic, Craig R., September 20, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Interpretation--Mallory, O. J., October 25, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Interpretation--Meekings, Donald C. (Visually Handicapped), August 23, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Interpretation--Meekings, Donald C., October 1988. (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Interpretation--Morton, Mary (Corrections), October 1988. (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Interpretation--Nunally, Tanya J. (State Lottery Dept.), August 2, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Interpretation--Osborne, Jimmy (Scott County), July 15, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Interpretation--Pier, Robert O. (Health), July 20, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Interpretation--Powell, Cleo, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Interpretation--Reeves, William (Transportation), May 1, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Interpretation--Smith, Donna A., May 17, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Interpretation--Spriggs, Virginia, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Interpretation--Stein, Suzanne E. (Fairfax County), April 6, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Interpretation--Stratman, Anna (Petersburg Circuit Court), September 5, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Interpretation--Sweeney, Patricia, August 27, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Interpretation--Thomas, Bruce P., April 13, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Interpretation--Thomas, Bruce P., August 4, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Interpretation--Thomas, Bruce P., August 24, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Interpretation--Washington, James J. (Virginia State University), April 1, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Interpretation--Worsham, Jacqueline (VCU), January 22, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Interpretation--Worsham, Jacqueline (VCU), September 9, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Interpretation--Yates, Larry D. (Health), July 20, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Interpretations, 1987-1988. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Interpretations, 1988-1989. (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Interpretations, 1989-1990. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Interpretations, 1990-1991. (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Interpretations, 1991-1992. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission Reports, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Layoff Cases, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Proposal, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Legalislative Proposal to Governor, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Letter and Agency Heads for Comments, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Local Entity Rulings, 1989-1990. (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Local Government Attorneys of Virginia, Inc., 1989. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lynchburg, May 10, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Lynchburg, May 11, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "M", 1988-1989. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Mailing Stickers, n.d.. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - MBE's Council on Status of Women, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Mediation #5, 1995-1998. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Mediation Services Focus Groups, February 12, 1998. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, August 23, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Notice, March 18, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - MHMRS, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - MH/MR/SAS, 1989. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous #2, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - National Public Employee Labor Relations Association, 1991-1994. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - New Agency Orientation Packet, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - New Grievance Procedure Drafts, 1995. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - ODU Attendance Policy Webb Center, 1988. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - ODU Discriminiation Complaints, 1987. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Old Dominion University, 1990-1996. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Pay for Performance Report, 1985. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Performance Measure Update, 2000 Legislation, September 13, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Personnel Communique Articles, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Planning and Budget, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Privacy Protection Act (Rudesyle, C. N., Jr.), February 7, 1989. (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Pro Bono, 1994. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Project Streamline, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Project Streamline #1, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - PS Action 37: Manpower Needs Career Development, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Public Notice Mailings, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Public Procurement, The Promise for Virginia's Future, Hearing Officer Decisions, 1998-1999. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Publication Costs, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Publication Practices of Virginia State Agencies--Senate Document No. 9, December 12, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Reappropriation Request, 2000 Legislation, September 20, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Reports to the Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1988-1989. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Reprisal, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Reprisal, 1987-1988. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Reprisal, 1987-1988. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Reprisal, 1989-1990. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Reprisal, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Reprisal--Beddingfield, Edna (Christopher Newport College), October 18, 1982. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Reprisal--Berry, Mike (MH/MR-Catawba), 1986. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Reprisal--Corell, Pamela G. (Dabney Lancaster Community College), September 27, 1983. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Reprisal--Graham, Zelda S., November 5, 1982. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Reprisal--Jeter, Mary, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Reprisal--Rudesyle, C. N., Jr. (Social Services), February 8, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Reprisal--Slahucka, William (MH/MR-Catawba), 1986. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Reprisal--Williams, Martha A. (Corrections), February 1981. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Reprisals, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Reprisals, 1983-1984. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Review of Grievance Panel Decisions, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Richmond, April 13, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Richmond, April 18, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Secretary's Task Force--Mediation, 1989. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sent to PCK, August 26, 1996. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Sixth Annual Administrative Law Conference, Richmond Crowne Plaza, May 25, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Social Services, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - State Board of Elections--Commission on Local Government, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - State Certification, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - State Milk Commission, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - State Police, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Substance Abuse, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Substance Abuse Training, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Survey of Agency Participants, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Survey Currents Masters, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Survey of Grievants, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Survey Results Masters, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Survey--Ronnie Jacobs, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on Continuous Quality Improvement, December 1993. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Task Force Mailings, 1994. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Task Force Membership, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Task Force Report--Final Copy, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Task Force Studying the Commonwealth's Grievance Procedure--Senate Documents, 1994. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Task Force Studying the Commonwealth's Grievance Procedure, 1994. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Taxation, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Training Notes--Outline, Schedules, Facilities Contacts, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Training Subcommittee, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Various Virginia Dept.'s Correspondence, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Veterans' Affairs--Supplement Retirement System, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Beach, May 9, 1995. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Code Commission, 1995. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Freedom of Information Act, Commuter Incentive Program, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Plan for Strengthening the Commonwealth's 21st Century Workforce, and Information Systems Development Program, March-April 1991. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Visually Handicapped/Hard of Hearing, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Volunteers for Panels, 1988. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Waste Management Emergency Services, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Western State Trial, 1984. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Accession 50472, 1980-2006.
    - ADR Council Report, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Adviceline Survey, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Agency Annual Reports, 1979-1998. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Agency Annual Reports, 1997-2000. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Agency Head meetings, FY 2002. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Agency History, 1987-2000. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Agency History/Ideas, 1987-2000. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Agency Regulatory Coordinator Info, FY 2003. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Agency Security Updates (Sonitrol-Security vendor), FY 2005. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Agency Training Metrics, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Applicant Flow Data Entry, 2002-2004. (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - August 19, 2002, FY 2003. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2005--2nd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2005--quarterly results. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--1st and 2nd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--1st and 2nd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--3rd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--3rd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--4th quarter. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Backup Documentation, FY 2006--4th quarter. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Board Profiles, 2002-2005. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Budget, FY 2002-2003. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Budget, FY 2004. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chesterfield Government Meeting, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Classification and Comp Reform Info, FY 2000. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cognistar Online CLE Course, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Comparative Data for EDR Programs, FY 2002-FY 2003. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Confidential SOA memos, FY 2003. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Services Response to DHRM, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Consulting Services Need Survey, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Contingency Management Survey, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Contract Employee Requirement, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Customer Service Survey Request, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Decision Packages, FY 2001. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors (DERC) in the 1980's, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DERC (Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors) History and Reports, 1986-1996. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - DHRM Contract Temp Employee Report Requirement, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 19)